rapidhomeremedies.com 2014-05-23

# Privacy Policy | Rapid Home Remedies

At http://www.rapidhomeremedies.com/, we always safe keep the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document relates to the kind of personal information received and collected by http://www.rapidhomeremedies.com/ and its uses.

**Log Files**  
www.rapidhomeremedies.com makes use of Log Files, similar to third party Websites. The Log File information include Internet Service Provider (ISP), Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, Date/Time Stamp, and Browser type, together with click numbers for analyzing trends, site administration, referring/exit pages, demographic information collection, and track movement of the user around the site. IP addresses and any other such data is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.rapidhomeremedies.com use cookies for storing information on record user-specific information on pages accessed or visited by the user, visitor’s preferences, information the visitor sends via their browser, or customize Web page content customization based on visitors’ browser type or other.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on information the visitor sends via their browser.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users, based on their visit to information visitor sends through their browser and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may keep out of the DART cookie use by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  
Few of our advertising partners may use web beacons and cookies on our site. Our advertising partners are …

**Google Adsense**  
The third-party ad networks and ad servers use technology for the advertisements and links that appear on www.rapidhomeremedies.com to be send directly to your browsers and when thi occur, they automatically receive your IP address. Other technologies (JavaScript, Cookies, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks for measuring the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or personalizing the advertising content that you see.

www.rapidhomeremedies.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You are advised to consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for information on their practices, and instructions for opting out of certain practices. www.rapidhomeremedies.com Privacy Policy does not apply to, and also we cannot control the activities of such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you can disable them using your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

At the browsers’ respective websites, more information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found.

For additional information or questions about our Privacy Policy, we request you to contact us by mailing at admin@rapidhomeremedies.com
